<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on Dylan Garrett</title>
    <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/other/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on Dylan Garrett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year} Dylan Garrett</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 21:36:44 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dylan-garrett.com/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>iOS App Support</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/other/ios-app-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 21:36:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/other/ios-app-support/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t officially provide support for my free apps. They are provided without warranty and are intended for use as-is. But you may contact me at app-support@dylan-garrett.com.
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Score Tracker Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/other/score-tracker-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 21:22:58 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/other/score-tracker-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy
Dylan Garrett built the Score Tracker for Watch app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Dylan Garrett at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
