<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Dylan Garrett</title>
    <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Dylan Garrett</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year} Dylan Garrett</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rust on a Digispark ATtiny85</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/rust-digispark-attiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/rust-digispark-attiny/</guid>
      <description>The Digistump Digispark is a tiny, simple, and cheap development board using the ATtiny85 MCU. While the official version is no longer for sale, clones are easily found online for around $2 each.&#xA;Rahix&amp;rsquo;s avr-hal already supports the ATtiny85 on the Adafruit Trinket board. The Trinket is nearly identical to the Digispark, but with a different USB bootloader, so avr-hal&amp;rsquo;s cargo run support won&amp;rsquo;t work. Instead, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to convert the output binary and deploy it with the micronucleus CLI tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Readwise Inline Tags</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/readwise-inline-tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/readwise-inline-tags/</guid>
      <description>The highlight-aggregation service Readwise supports a feature called inline tagging, which allows front-loading the work of organizing highlights by adding tags to highlight notes. Beyond plain tagging, Readwise supports several special action tags.&#xA;Readwise documentation on this feature is sparse and spread across several locations, so here is a summary.&#xA;Action tags Action Tag Description .cN Concatenate highlights 1 (&amp;quot;.c1 + .c2&amp;quot;, &amp;ldquo;.c1 + .c2 + .c3&amp;rdquo;) .hN Heading level 2 (.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Technology</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/constrained-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/constrained-technology/</guid>
      <description>The enemy of art is the absence of limitations. — Orson Welles&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;d like to share some of my favorite constrained technologies. Technologies that I believe are better because of, and not despite, their limitations.&#xA;e-Ink E-ink insists on a certain interaction model. Grey-scale rather than full color pushes one toward text and informative illustrations. Slow refresh enforces pages of static content rather than endless scrolling of attention-grabbing content. These nudges transfer control back to the reader and make e-ink my favorite display technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doom Fire in LÖVE/lua</title>
      <link>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/doom-fire-love2d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dylan-garrett.com/blog/doom-fire-love2d/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I read Fabien Sanglard&amp;rsquo;s post describing how the fire effect was implemented in Doom on the Playstation 1 and I figured this was a good chance to implement a small toy program in LÖVE. Here&amp;rsquo;s an iterative tutorial, written for beginners, to demonstrate implementing this effect using Lua in the LÖVE environment. If you&amp;rsquo;re already experienced with Lua or programming in general then go read Fabien&amp;rsquo;s post. It&amp;rsquo;s much more succinct.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
